https://www.palmapictures.es/data-protection-policy/

Company
Corporate name: PALMA PICTURES, S.L.
Postal address: Calle Siurells, 4, CP. 07141 Marratxí (Palma de Mallorca)
Telephone number: +34 971 226 232
Email: mailbox@palmapictures.es
Purpose
How will we use your data?
The following Privacy Policy establishes the terms by which we manage personal data at PALMA PICTURES, S.L; this includes any personal data collected through our website https://www.palmapictures.es/, as well as any other data that is handled in our work as a business.
PALMA PICTURES, S.L; collects the following personal data for the purposes indicated below:
Casting: your data will only be handled in order to classify in the most detailed way possible those who are interested in participating in certain projects, so as to facilitate selection by our clients.
Property owners: your data will only be handled to record graphic references of the most relevant elements of the properties and enable us to contact you regarding possible projects.
Production: your data will only be handled to create the necessary documents to organize shoots, putting different crew members from the same shoot in contact.
Clients: client data will only be handled in relation to creating production documents, newsletters and marketing material.
Newsletter: your data will only be handled in relation to the distribution of our newsletters and marketing materials.
Personal data of candidates: data provided by potential candidates on CVs, cover letters, emails or in job interviews will be used to cover possible job vacancies in our company. In the instance of being hired by our company, your data will be used only to manage the labour relationship with PALMA PICTURES, S.L.
For how long do we store your data?
Our databases are used primarily to contact different interested parties, thus the rest of the data may change and be updated frequently. In all cases we will keep personal data in our systems for the duration of the relation with the interested data subject.
For data relating to work, the information will be handled during the professional relationship and once concluded, for the necessary time to respond to possible incomplete requirements. In the case of you having sent us your CV or attending an interview for a job vacancy, your personal information will be stored for a period of one year, after which, having not been selected, the information will be deleted from our systems.
The data provided for the distribution of the newsletters and marketing materials will be kept until you notify us of your wish to no longer receive communications from us. You can exercise this right to refuse further communication via the channels indicated in this Privacy Policy.
Legitimization
The legitimization for the handling of data relating to participants in castings, location property owners, and potential crew members is the consent of the interested party.
In the case of children under 14 years old, we will not handle their data without the express and prior consent of the parents or legal guardians.
Personal information of employees will be handled in relation to contractual obligations.
The legal basis for the handling of personal data for the distribution of the newsletter is the consent of the interested party.
Recipients
Release of data to third parties
With the exception of legal obligations that can force us to release data to third parties, the personal data of those who participate in our productions may be released to third parties who participate in the same (for example catering service). Apart from these two instances, we will never release personal information to third parties, without the express and prior consent of the data subject.
Types of data
Types of data handled:
Castings:
Name and surname(s).
DNI (ID number).
Mailing address.
Email address.
Telephone number.
Date of birth.
Sex.
Physical characteristics (including height, weight, garment size and shoe size).
Work experience.
Photographs.
Social security number.
Bank details.
Property owners:
Name and surname(s).
Email address.
Telephone number.
Photographs of property.
Geolocation of property.
Clients:
Name and surname(s).
Mailing address.
Email address.
Telephone number.
Newsletter:
Name and surname(s).
E-mail address.
Name of company.
Candidates:
Name and surname(s).
DNI (ID number).
Mailing address.
Email address.
Telephone number.
Photo.
Nationality.
Sex.
Date of birth.
Academic history.
Professional history.
Surveillance video:
Photo/video footage.
Voice.
Rights
You have the right to:
Edit your personal data.
Request via email that your personal data be removed.
Lodge a complaint regarding your rights with the Spanish Data Protection Agency (Agencia Española de Protección de Datos) or with the autonomous data protection agency, if one exists.
Be informed of any security incident that may affect your data protection rights.
Restrict processing of your personal data.
Data portability.
Information on Data Protection
Company
Corporate name: PALMA PICTURES, S.L.
Postal address: Calle Siurells, 4, CP. 07141 Marratxí (Palma de Mallorca)
Telephone number: +34 971 226 232
Email: mailbox@palmapictures.es
Purpose
How will we use your data?
The following Privacy Policy establishes the terms by which we manage personal data at PALMA PICTURES, S.L; this includes any personal data collected through our website https://www.palmapictures.es/, as well as any other data that is handled in our work as a business.
PALMA PICTURES, S.L; collects the following personal data for the purposes indicated below:
Casting: your data will only be handled in order to classify in the most detailed way possible those who are interested in participating in certain projects, so as to facilitate selection by our clients.
Property owners: your data will only be handled to record graphic references of the most relevant elements of the properties and enable us to contact you regarding possible projects.
Production: your data will only be handled to create the necessary documents to organize shoots, putting different crew members from the same shoot in contact.
Clients: client data will only be handled in relation to creating production documents, newsletters and marketing material.
Newsletter: your data will only be handled in relation to the distribution of our newsletters and marketing materials.
Personal data of candidates: data provided by potential candidates on CVs, cover letters, emails or in job interviews will be used to cover possible job vacancies in our company. In the instance of being hired by our company, your data will be used only to manage the labour relationship with PALMA PICTURES, S.L.
For how long do we store your data?
Our databases are used primarily to contact different interested parties, thus the rest of the data may change and be updated frequently. In all cases we will keep personal data in our systems for the duration of the relation with the interested data subject.
For data relating to work, the information will be handled during the professional relationship and once concluded, for the necessary time to respond to possible incomplete requirements. In the case of you having sent us your CV or attending an interview for a job vacancy, your personal information will be stored for a period of one year, after which, having not been selected, the information will be deleted from our systems.
The data provided for the distribution of the newsletters and marketing materials will be kept until you notify us of your wish to no longer receive communications from us. You can exercise this right to refuse further communication via the channels indicated in this Privacy Policy.
Legitimization
The legitimization for the handling of data relating to participants in castings, location property owners, and potential crew members is the consent of the interested party.
In the case of children under 14 years old, we will not handle their data without the express and prior consent of the parents or legal guardians.
Personal information of employees will be handled in relation to contractual obligations.
The legal basis for the handling of personal data for the distribution of the newsletter is the consent of the interested party.
Recipients
Release of data to third parties
With the exception of legal obligations that can force us to release data to third parties, the personal data of those who participate in our productions may be released to third parties who participate in the same (for example catering service). Apart from these two instances, we will never release personal information to third parties, without the express and prior consent of the data subject.
Types of data
Types of data handled:
Castings:
Name and surname(s).
DNI (ID number).
Mailing address.
Email address.
Telephone number.
Date of birth.
Sex.
Physical characteristics (including height, weight, garment size and shoe size).
Work experience.
Photographs.
Social security number.
Bank details.
Property owners:
Name and surname(s).
Email address.
Telephone number.
Photographs of property.
Geolocation of property.
Clients:
Name and surname(s).
Mailing address.
Email address.
Telephone number.
Newsletter:
Name and surname(s).
E-mail address.
Name of company.
Candidates:
Name and surname(s).
DNI (ID number).
Mailing address.
Email address.
Telephone number.
Photo.
Nationality.
Sex.
Date of birth.
Academic history.
Professional history.
Surveillance video:
Photo/video footage.
Voice.
Rights
You have the right to:
Edit your personal data.
Request via email that your personal data be removed.
Lodge a complaint regarding your rights with the Spanish Data Protection Agency (Agencia Española de Protección de Datos) or with the autonomous data protection agency, if one exists.
Be informed of any security incident that may affect your data protection rights.
Restrict processing of your personal data.
Data portability.
Copyright palmapictures 2020 - All Rights Reserved.
Web development by adPalma
Back To Top
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.Cookie settingsCookie PolicyACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
